const quizDataHukisoku = [
    {
      question: "nosotros | estar",
      1: "es",
      2: "somos",
      3: "sois",
      correct: 2,
      display: "nosotros somos",
    },
    {
      question: "estar | yo",
      1: "estoy",
      2: "estás",
      3: "estan",
      correct: 1,
      display: "yo estoy",
    },
    {
      question: "poder | ustedes",
      1: "pueden",
      2: "puede",
      3: "podéis",
      correct: 1,
      display: "ustedes pueden",
    },
    {
      question: "dar | él",
      1: "damos",
      2: "dais",
      3: "da",
      correct: 3,
      display: "él da",
    },
    {
      question: "saber | yo",
      1: "sabes",
      2: "sé",
      3: "sabemos",
      correct: 2,
      display: "yo sé",
    },
    {
      question: "conocer | yo",
      1: "conoce",
      2: "conozco",
      3: "conocéis",
      correct: 2,
      display: "yo conozco",
    },
    {
      question: "querer | nosotras",
      1: "quiere",
      2: "queremos",
      3: "quieren",
      correct: 2,
      display: "nosotras queremos",
    },
    {
      question: "venir | vosotras",
      1: "viene",
      2: "venimos",
      3: "venís",
      correct: 3,
      display: "vosotras venís",
    },
    {
      question: "sentir | tú",
      1: "sientes",
      2: "sienten",
      3: "sentís",
      correct: 1,
      display: "tú sientes",
    },
    {
      question: "poner | yo",
      1: "ponrd",
      2: "pongo",
      3: "pone",
      correct: 2,
      display: "yo pongo",
    },
  ];
 
  export { quizDataHukisoku };